vistastartmenu.com 2016-03-15

# Privacy Policy

**Policy on Privacy and Personal Information Use**   
Introduction  
OrdinarySoft respects each individual's right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site and products only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at OrdinarySoft's Web site, and through OrdinarySoft enabled software.

Part I. Information Collection  
OrdinarySoft collects information through our Web site at several points. We collect the following information about casual visitors: the IP address of the visiting machine for "geographic" statistical purposes only.

We may also collect names and email addresses that our users divulge about other people, such as referrals or business leads. OrdinarySoft does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information.

We collect the following general data that is not personally identifiable information: pages visited, date and time.

We collect registration data by means of voluntary submition for the sole purpose of providing our users, both Customers and Vendors, with our services, and for that purpose only.

We collect this information through registration forms, clickstream tracking, automatic logging files, and other similar methods. Personal information is collected through Registration Forms. Pages visited, dates and times are collected via clickstream tracking and logging files. The personal information is collected voluntarily. To receive our products and services, personal information is mandatory because it is used to accurately build a customer profile and for communication with the customer. Other information we request is optional.

OrdinarySoft collects information through OrdinarySoft enabled software at several points. We collect the following information about software users: the IP address of the visiting machine and the computer host name for "geographic" statistical purposes and account verification only, we also collect the usage of previously identified software actions and activities for the purpose of piracy protection, and to enable the OrdinarySoft pay-per-use functionality as discussed on each product's license agreement.

We collect software usage information by means of the PlimWare module that is incorporated with each software package and logging files. The personal information is collected voluntarily; usage information is collected in accordance with the software license agreement. To receive our products and services, personal information is mandatory because it is used to accurately identify an account and for communicating with the user. Usage information is collected to supply the user with licensing terms and entitlement as defined in the software license agreement. Other information we request is optional.

We employ cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user's computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable OrdinarySoft to automatically login a user back to our services provided he/she choose to enable such option. Our cookies do not have an expiration date. Our cookies collect personally identifiable information, specifically the username and password for automatic logon.

Part II. Information Usage  
The information collected by OrdinarySoft will be used solely by OrdinarySoft and in conjunction with the specified terms in this document. Users who provide information may receive email announcements regarding OrdinarySoft' services from time to time.

Registered customers may receive additional announcements from us about products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our customers we present the option to not receive these types of communications.

The information we collect will be used to create customer profiles based on browsing or purchasing history. We may supplement information collected at our Web site with data from other sources such as credit history to authorize purchases.

OrdinarySoft will not share data with any third party entity or individual, except usage information to our vendors as specified in each software license agreement.

We offer links to other Web sites. Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours.

Our Web site offers forums and message boards. Please be advised that information posted in these venues becomes public knowledge.

If our policy on information collection or uses changes, will advise you by posting a dated copy here or if you are a registered user then you will be advised via email.

Part III. Access to Information  
OrdinarySoft maintains the accuracy of our information by providing the user instant access to it and allowing updates to take effect immediately. Registered customers may access their own personal information via our login pages, both for Customers and Vendors and update any inaccuracies they may find. Users may choose to remove their information from our database by contacting us in writing at: OrdinarySoft@gmail.com

Part IV. Problem Resolution  
If problems arise, customers and sellers may contact OrdinarySoft by phone, email or mail, see here for more information. We are committed to resolving disputes within 2 business days.

Part V. Data Storage and Security  
OrdinarySoft protects user information both in our servers and on the users computer with the following security measures: registry data encryption, data file encryption, secure servers, firewalls, SSL encryption and other proprietary technologies and procedures used to protect consumer privacy.

If you have any further questions about privacy or security, please contact us by sending an email to: OrdinarySoft@gmail.com.
